{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 5.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0)",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0)",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is 4.8.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.8. The .NET framework is a software framework that provides a platform for developing and running applications on Windows and other platforms. It includes a large library of reusable components, such",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.8. The .NET framework is a software framework that provides a platform for developing and running applications on Windows and other platforms. It includes a large library of reusable components, such",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.5.2. The .NET Framework is a software framework that supports the development of applications and services that run on Windows and other platforms. It includes a large library of reusable",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.1",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "9.0",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 7 is the most recent major version of the .NET Framework. It was released on November 8, 2022, and is the successor to .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is 4.7.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.5.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is 4.5.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0 was released on November 8, 2021.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.8. The .NET framework is a software framework that provides a platform for developing and running applications. It includes a large library of classes and APIs that developers can use to build their",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0 was released on November 8, 2021.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET Framework 4.5.2",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 4.5.2",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 4.5.2",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 4.5.2",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET Framework 4.5.2 is the most recent major version of the .NET Framework.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 4.5.2 is the most recent major version of the .NET Framework.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 6.0 is the most recent major version of the .NET Framework. It was released on November 8, 2021, and is the successor to .NET 5.0.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.8.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET Framework is .NET 6.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.7.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.7.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.5.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The most recent major version of the .NET framework is 4.7.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET Framework 4.8 is the most recent major version of the .NET Framework.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET Framework 4.8 is the most recent major version of the .NET Framework.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.2",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.1.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.2.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.1.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.1.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 9.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 4.5.2",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "4.8.1.",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": ".NET 4.5.2",
            "needle": "The latest major version of the .NET framework is .NET 9.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "What is the latest major version of the .NET framework?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}